Subject Files
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  - Subject files: Skiing (Strawberry Hill), undated; 16 (Box 1557)
    - [Lowell Thomas watching a man ski off a jump], 12
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing], 13
    - [A man going off a ski jump], 14
    - [Skiiers walking up a slope], 15
    - [The ski slope], 16
    - [View of the ski slope], 17
    - [Lowell Thomas and friends on a ski trip], 18
    - [Lowell Thomas and a group of men sitting on a porch], 19
    - [Two men sitting outside having lunch at the ski resort], 20
  Box 1558
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  - Subject files: Skiing (Sun Valley), circa 1940s - 1970s; 1 (Box 1558)
    - A memory from January 1970, Sun Valley, 1
    - Verso: A memory from January 1970, Sun Valley, 1-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas, Gretchen Fraser, Otto Lang], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas, Gretchen Fraser, Otto Lang], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas, Gretchen Fraser, Otto Lang], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas, Jr. and Gretchen Fraser], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas, Jr. and Gretchen Fraser], 6
    - Johnny Litchfield, Rudy Matt, LT, Sigi Engl [1951], 7
    - Verso: Johnny Litchfield, Rudy Matt, LT, Sigi Engl [1951], 7-verso
    - Verso: May 14, 1951 [Wendell Corey, Lowell Thomas, Stewart Granger], 8
    - Verso: May 14, 1951, 8-verso
    - Caption: Mar 23 [19]51 [Wendell Corey, Lowell Thomas, Stewart Granger], 9
    - Caption: Mar 23 [19]51 [Wendell Corey, Lowell Thomas, Stewart Granger], 10
    - Verso: May 14, 1951, 10-verso
    - Caption: Mar 23 [19]51 [Wendell Corey, Lowell Thomas, Stewart Granger], 11
    - Caption: Mar 23 [19]51 [Wendell Corey, Lowell Thomas, Stewart Granger], 12
    - Caption: Mar 23 [19]51 [Wendell Corey, Lowell Thomas, Stewart Granger], 13
    - Verso: May 14, 1951, 13-verso
    - Caption: Mar 23 [19]51 [Wendell Corey, Lowell Thomas, Stewart Granger], 14
    - [Lowell Thomas talking to people at an event], 15
    - [Lowell Thomas getting up to make a speech], 16
    - [Two men on a ski trip], 17
    - [Lowell Thomas going off a ski jump], 18
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man at the podium, 19
    - [Skiiers on a slope], 20
    - [A group of skiiers standing in front of "The Ram"], 21
    - [Man skiing down a slope], 22
    - [Two people skiing], 23
    - [People skiing down a slope], 24
  - Subject files: Skiing (Thomas family), circa 1930s; 2 (Box 1558)
    - March - 1939; Jackson, N.H. [New Hampshire], 1
    - Verso: March - 1939; Jackson, N.H. [New Hampshire], 1-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas and two other skiiers], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas and two other guys skiing], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. (?) skiing], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas and his family], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas, Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas, and Lowell Thomas Jr.], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas on skis], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas on skis], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas on skis], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas and two other on skis], 10
    - [Sled dog team], 11
    - [Sled dogs pulling a sled], 12
    - [Snow-covered field], 13
  - Subject files: Skiing (Utah) [includes color photograph], undated; 3 (Box 1558)
    - Note: Christl [Thalhammer]; Skiing - Alta [envelope that contained items 3.2-3.7], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas and two others on skis, 2
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas stuck in the snow], 4
    - [Man skiing], 5
    - Note: put in winter sports pix; Mr. and Mrs. Alf Engen, L T and Christl [Thalhammer], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas and others on a ski slope], 7
    - LT - Mt. Superior, famous for its avalanches, near Alta, Utah. Twice I was cut off by avalanches crashing down this mountain. L.T., 8
    - Verso: LT - Mt. Superior, famous for its avalanches, near Alta, Utah. Twice I was cut off by avalanches crashing down this mountain. L.T., 8-verso
    - With Hack Miller, "Mr. Utah," my ski coach, 9
    - Note: With Hack Miller, "Mr. Utah," my ski coach, 10
    - Felix Koziol, director Wasatch Forestry Service; Mr. and Mrs. Alf Engen, and L.T. - at Alta.; Alf one time 4-way ski champ of America. He's one of greatest ever, 11
    - Verso: Felix Koziol, director Wasatch Forestry Service; Mr. and Mrs. Alf Engen, and L.T. - at Alta.; Alf one time 4-way ski champ of America. He's one of greatest ever, 11-verso
    - On May 28th snow still so deep at Alta we could lean on top of lamp posts! Hack Miller and Chic Morton, 12
    - Verso: On May 28th snow still so deep at Alta we could lean on top of lamp posts! Hack Miller and Chic Morton, 12-verso
    - This is another picture of the same mountain. The people are in the way. But it may help you a bit. It isn't the picture I had in mind. Hope to find what I want and add it to this collection, 13
    - Verso: This is another picture of the same mountain. The people are in the way. But it may help you a bit. It isn't the picture I had in mind. Hope to find what I want and add it to this collection, 13-verso
    - March 9, 1974, Snowbird Utah, 14
    - Verso: March 9, 1974, Snowbird Utah, 14-verso
    - Ray Johnson, 15
    - Verso: Ray Johnson, 15-verso
    - With Ray Johnson, Park City, 1975, 16
    - Verso: With Ray Johnson, Park City, 1975, 16-verso
    - 1976, Alta, 17
    - Verso: 1976, Alta, 17-verso
    - Lowell Thomas (visits Park City) 1-2-1964, 18
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas (visits Park City) 1-2-1964, 18-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing at Park City], 19
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing at Park City], 20
    - Photo by Hack Miller, Desert News, Salt Lake City, Utah, 21
    - Verso: Photo by Hack Miller, Desert News, Salt Lake City, Utah, 21-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing], 22
    - [[Lowell Thomas skiing down a slope], 23
    - Hank Miller, Desert News, 24
    - Verso: Hank Miller, Desert News, 24-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas standing on his skis], 25
    - LT at Alta in the Wasatch Mts. One of my top favorite areas!, 26
    - Verso: LT at Alta in the Wasatch Mts. One of my top favorite areas!, 26-verso
    - LT with Messers. Engen, Dyhrenfurth and Gabriel, 27
    - Verso: LT with Messers. Engen, Dyhrenfurth and Gabriel, 27-verso
    - [left to right: Alf Engen, Norman Dyhrenfurth, Lowell Thomas and [?] Gabriel], 28
    - [left to right: Norman Dyhrenfurth, Lowell Thomas and [?] Gabriel], 29
    - [left to right: Norman Dyhrenfurth, Lowell Thomas and [?] Gabriel], 30
  - Subject files: Skiing (Utah) [includes color photographs], undated; 4 (Box 1558)
    - [4 copies] LT and 2 foot Shortee skis - also at Alta, Utah, 1
    - Verso: LT and 2 foot Shortee skis - also at Alta, Utah, 1-verso
    - L.T. with Richard Bass, Snowbird, Alta, Utah, 2
    - Verso: L.T. with Richard Bass, Snowbird, Alta, Utah, 2-verso
    - [Stein Eriksen, left, Lowell Thomas, right] Verso: Hank Miller Photo 1973, 3
    - Verso: Hank Miller Photo 1973, 3-verso
    - [Stein Eriksen, left, Lowell Thomas, right] Verso: Hank Miller Photo 1973, 4
    - Verso: Hank Miller Photo 1973, 4-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas, left, Stein Eriksen, right], 5
    - Photo by Tom Plofchan; Photohaus; Alta, Utah 84070; Group Shot #4 LTOLAE, 6
    - Verso: Photo by Tom Plofchan; Photohaus; Alta, Utah 84070; Group Shot #4 LTOLAE, 6-verso
    - Photo by Tom Plofchan; Photohaus; Alta, Utah 84070; Group Shot #5 LTOLAE, 7
    - Verso: Photo by Tom Plofchan; Photohaus; Alta, Utah 84070; Group Shot #5 LTOLAE, 7-verso
    - Photo by Tom Plofchan; Photohaus; Alta, Utah 84070; Photographed in the Wasatch National Forest, "The Photohaus" Alta, Utah, 8
    - Verso: Photo by Tom Plofchan; Photohaus; Alta, Utah 84070; Photographed in the Wasatch National Forest, "The Photohaus" Alta, Utah, 8-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas and his dog on a skip slope], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas in front of a "Ski Utah" sign], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas and another man on skis], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting on the porch with his skis], 12
    - [Lowell Thomas talking to a man at the ski slope], 13
    - [Lowell Thomas in a race at Alta ski area in Utah], 14
    - Verso: 1973, 15
    - Verso: 1973, 15-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with a man at a ski resort], 16
    - [Man skiing off the edge of a cliff], 17
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man on skis], 18
    - [Lowell Thomas and with another man on skis], 19
    - [Lowell Thomas leaning ona railing with his skis], 20
    - [avalanche], 21
    - [Lowell Thomas with a man holding a trophy], 22
  - Subject files: Skiing (with Lowell Thomas), 1926 - circa 1940s; 5 (Box 1558)
    - LT at Clover Brook in 1926, 1
    - Verso: LT at Clover Brook in 1926, 1-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas standing in front of a snowy pine tree], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting with three men in the woods], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas (?) standing in the snow with skis], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas and three men standing in the snow], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man on skis], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas standing at the base of a cliff], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas standing at the base of a cliff], 8
    - [Five men skiing], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas and others getting ready to ski], 10
  - Subject files: Skiing (with Lowell Thomas) [includes color photographs], circa 1940s - 1970s; 6 (Box 1558)
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing down a slope], 1
    - [Person skiing], 2
    - [Person skiing down a slope], 3
    - [Skiier going down a slope], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas and two other skiiers], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting at a table with others at a ski resort], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas and two others sitting on the railing at a ski resort], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas writing on a paper while four men stand behind him], 8
    - [People carrying their skis through the snow], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas skiing], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas looking at his ski], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas and two fellow skiiers and Lowell Thomas skiing down a hill], 12
    - [Photos of Lowell Thomas skiing], 13
    - [Lowell Thomas buried in the snow], 14
    - [Lowell Thomas carrying his skis], 15
    - [Lowell Thomas in his ski gear], 16
    - [Lowell Thomas carrying his skis], 17
    - [Lowell Thomas holding his skis], 18
    - [Lowell Thomas and a young boy], 19
    - [Lowell Thomas], 20
    - [Lowell Thomas], 21
    - [Lowell Thomas talking to two people], 22
    - [A painting of Lowell Thomas], 23
    - [A Lowell Thomas showcase], 24
    - [Lowell Thomas with his skis], 25
    - [Lowell Thomas and his dog on a ski lift], 26
  - Skiing (with Lowell Thomas) [includes color photographs], 1942 - circa 1970s; 7 (Box 1558)
    - Photographer: Partridge - Pico - Powder Falls[?] (l. to r.) Hubert Stevens, L. Thomas [Jr.], Janet Mead, Lowell Thomas, Marquis d'Albizzi, Jan 4, 1942, 1
    - Verso: Photographer: Partridge - Pico - Powder Falls[?] (l. to r.) Hubert Stevens, L. Thomas [Jr.], Janet Mead, Lowell Thomas, Marquis d'Albizzi, Jan 4, 1942, 1-verso
    - Herbert Stevens, 2
    - Note: Herbert Stevens, 3
    - Hubert Stevens; Verso: Only blow up only the 4 in the middle! L.T., 4
    - Verso: Only blow up only the 4 in the middle! L.T., 4-verso
    - Tucson, 1944?, 5
    - Verso: Tucson, 1944?, 5-verso
    - Joe Ryan on right, LT in center, ? on left; Verso: Pic by John O'[?]; M. Ryan, J.B. Ryan [left], The Hon. On[?]sime Gagnon [right], Lowell Thomas, 6
    - Verso: Pic by John O'[?]; M. Ryan, J.B. Ryan [left], The Hon. On[?]sime Gagnon [right], Lowell Thomas, 6-verso
    - Note: Joe Ryan on right, LT in center, ? on left, 7
    - L.T. the skier. Took up skiing after 40 years of age. Took the headwall at Tuckerman Ravine on LT's 50th birthday, 8
    - Verso: L.T. the skier. Took up skiing after 40 years of age. Took the headwall at Tuckerman Ravine on LT's 50th birthday, 8-verso
    - Jim Parker (left) who was drowned in the unexplored rapids of the Indus. Cut out 2 men on right; Verso: Jim Parker, L.T., Sepp Ruschp and Jack Sawyer, 9
    - Verso: Jim Parker, L.T., Sepp Ruschp and Jack Sawyer, 9-verso
    - Note: Jim Parker (left) who was drowned in the unexplored rapids of the Indus. Cut out 2 men on right, 10
    - Joe Ryan[?] on right, 11
    - Verso: Joe Ryan[?] on right, 11-verso
    - Canadian Pacific Railway Photo; Leading Winter Sports Personalities: Lowell Thomas, second from right, noted radio commentator and familiar figure on Eastern Canadian ski slopes for many years, is welcomed to the Lac Beauport booth at the recent International Winter Sports Show in New York by Fritz Loosli, director of the Chateau Frontenac Ski Hawk School, and Fritz and Marili Tschannen, in costume. Tschannen, holder of the world's ski-jumping record for three years and winner of 362 first prizes in the national and international ski competitions, will instruct in the Loosli school at Lac Beauport this Winter; Verso: Tschaennens, Loosli and Thomas, 12
    - Verso: Tschaennens, Loosli and Thomas, 12-verso
    - Note: Canadian Pacific Railway Photo; Leading Winter Sports Personalities: Lowell Thomas, second from right, noted radio commentator and familiar figure on Eastern Canadian ski slopes for many years, is welcomed to the Lac Beauport booth at the recent International Winter Sports Show in New York by Fritz Loosli, director of the Chateau Frontenac Ski Hawk School, and Fritz and Marili Tschannen, in costume. Tschannen, holder of the world's ski-jumping record for three years and winner of 362 first prizes in the national and international ski competitions, will instruct in the Loosli school at Lac Beauport this Winter, 13
    - Monte Atwater "Piff" (avalanche dog) Ed La Chappelle, 14
    - Verso: Monte Atwater "Piff" (avalanche dog) Ed La Chappelle, 14-verso
    - Lowell Thomas, 15
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas, 15-verso
    - Hunter Harris, Wayne Poulsen, LT, Otto Lang, 16
    - Verso: Hunter Harris, Wayne Poulsen, LT, Otto Lang, 16-verso
    - LT and Producer Otto Lang, 17
    - Verso: LT and Producer Otto Lang, 17-verso
    - Ernie McCullough, Aspen Downhill Champion, the day he won the title on the Nose Dive, at Stowe, VT. [Vermont], Mar. 1952, 18
    - Verso: Ernie McCullough, Aspen Downhill Champion, the day he won the title on the Nose Dive, at Stowe, VT. [Vermont], Mar. 1952, 18-verso
    - Dave McCoy, 19
    - Verso: Dave McCoy, 19-verso
    - [Dave McCoy], 20
    - [Dave McCoy], 21
    - [Lowell Thomas walking next to man on ski trip?], 22
    - Col. Bernt Balchen, L. T. and Erling Strom, 23
    - Verso: Col. Bernt Balchen, L. T. and Erling Strom, 23-verso
    - Photo by Mel Schieltz; Mayor Corrigan, Bob Beattie, Thayer Tutt, Gov. John Love and John Stalder, Pres. Of Cherry Hills Country Club, 24
    - Verso: Photo by Mel Schieltz; Mayor Corrigan, Bob Beattie, Thayer Tutt, Gov. John Love and John Stalder, Pres. Of Cherry Hills Country Club, 24-verso
    - LT and Alf Engen, 25
    - Verso: LT and Alf Engen, 25-verso
    - LT and Pierre Trudeau, 26
    - Verso: LT and Pierre Trudeau, 26-verso
    - Lowell Thomas with his long-time friend Frank Elkins who wrote for the New York Times [note that stated this is missing], 27
    - Verso: 1967, 28
    - Verso: 1967, 28-verso
    - Jim and Shane McConkey and a great friend!, 29
    - Verso: Jim and Shane McConkey and a great friend!, 29-verso
    - Spring 1979, 30
    - Verso: Spring 1979, 30-verso
    - With Dick Durrance in British Columbia, 31
    - Note: With Dick Durrance in British Columbia, 32
    - Note: For your picture file (from George R. Senner, Seattle, Washington), [likely contained photographs, 33
    - [Lowell Thomas, left, Steiner Eriksen, right], 34
    - [Lowell Thomas, left, Steiner Eriksen, right], 35
    - [Lowell Thomas, left, Steiner Eriksen, right], 36
    - [Lowell Thomas, left, Steiner Eriksen, right], 37
    - [Lowell Thomas and a group talking to Steiner Eriksen], 38
    - [Lowell Thomas, Steiner Eriksen, and another man], 39
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man], 40
  - Subject files: Skiing (with Lowell Thomas) [includes color photographs], circa 1950s - 1970s; 8 (Box 1558)
    - [left to right: Lowell Thomas, Lowell Thomas, Jr., Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas and Mrs. Marianna Thomas], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas, right, Mrs. Marianna Thomas, center], 3
    - [left to right] Fred Iselin, Christl Thalhammer, Lowell Thomas, 4
    - Verso: [left to right] Fred Iselin, Christl Thalhammer, Lowell Thomas, 4-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas, Jr., left, Lowell Thomas, right], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas, Jr., left, Lowell Thomas, right], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas and two other skiiers], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas and two men talking], 8
    - [Three men on the ski slope talking], 9
    - [Three skiiers looking at something], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas and two others on the ski slope], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas and two other standing in the snow], 12
    - [Lowell Thomas and four other skiiers standing in the snow], 13
    - [Lowell Thomas and three other skiiers], 14
    - [Lowell Thomas and three other skiiers], 15
    - [Lowell Thomas and two others skiing], 16
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with three other skiiers], 17
    - [Lowell Thomas and two others on skis], 18
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man on skis], 19
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man], 20
    - [Lowell Thoomas on skis with his arm around a man], 21
    - [Lowell Thomas pointing out something to a man], 22
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man standing in front of a sign], 23
    - [Lowell Thomas and a woman on skis], 24
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man on the slopes], 25
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man on skis], 26
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man at a ski slope], 27
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking to two men on skis], 28
    - [A group of young men on skis], 29
    - [Lowell Thomas stuck on the snow], 30
    - [Lowell Thomas talking to two peoplpe holding skis], 31
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with a man on the slopes], 32
    - [Lowell Thomas and four men standing in a ski slope], 33
    - [Photos from Lowell Thomas's skiing], 34
  - Subject files: Skiing (with Lowell Thomas) [color photographs], circa 1950s - 1970s; 9 (Box 1558)
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with a man in front of the ski lodge], 1
    - [A man waving], 2
    - [A man standing in front of a house], 3
    - [A man], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas and others a t a ski resort], 5
    - [Lowell thomas standing with his friends at a ski resort], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas and two other skiiers], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas and four fellow skiiers standing in front of the lodge], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas and other sitting outside the ski lodge talking], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with a man at a ski resort], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas and two others with a trophy], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with others at a ski resort], 12
  - Subject files: Skiing (without Lowell Thomas) [includes color photographs], undated; 10 (Box 1558)
    - [Kamloops, British Columbia], 1
    - Note: Kamloops, British Columbia, 2
    - [Kamloops, British Columbia], 3
    - [Kamloops, British Columbia], 4
    - [Kamloops, British Columbia], 5
    - Otto L- [Lang?], 6
    - Verso: Otto L- [Lang?], 6-verso
    - Luggi and Wayne P., 7
    - Verso: Luggi and Wayne P., 7-verso
    - Washburn and Lowell Thomas, Jr., 8
    - Note: Washburn and Lowell Thomas, Jr., 9
    - Sig Buchmayer[Buchmayr] executes an acrobatic jump on the Tuckerman Headwall, 10
    - Note: Sig Buchmayer[Buchmayr] executes an acrobatic jump on the Tuckerman Headwall, 11
    - Tom Murstad in Norway, 12
    - Verso: Tom Murstad in Norway, 12-verso
    - [A group of skiiers], 13
    - [A group of skiiers], 14
    - [Scenic view of a snowy mountain reflected in a lake], 15
    - [Woman on lake, snowy mountain in background], 16
    - [Man on a snowy mountain], 17
    - [Two men standing with skis], 18
    - [Two skiiers on top of a mountain], 19
    - [Skiiers on top of a snowy mountain], 20
    - [Avalance], 21
    - [Avalance], 22
    - [Woman skiing], 23
    - [Man and woman skiing], 24
    - [Man reading "Invitation to Skiing" while skiing], 25
    - [Group of skiiers on top of a mountain], 26
    - [People skiing], 27
    - [A dog], [2 copies], 28
    - [A person going off a ski jump], 29
    - [Man skiing], 30
    - [Woman on skis], 31
    - [Two mens skiing], 32
    - [Man and woman carrying skis], 33
  - Subject files: Skiing film shoot [color photographs], 1970s; 11 (Box 1558)
    - [Lowell Thomas and man with skis], 1
    - [Cameraman], 2
    - [Man micing Lowell Thomas], 3
    - [A house through the trees], 4
  Box 1559
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  - Subject files: Sledding, circa 1930s; 1 (Box 1559)
    - [People sledding], 1
    - [Sled being pulled by dogs], 2
  - Subject files: Sleepy Hollow, undated; 2 (Box 1559)
    - To Gene Hollmann, 1
    - Verso: To Gene Hollmann, 1-verso
    - [Two men wearing flase beards], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas dressed on costume], 3
  - Subject files: Eric Sloane and Lowell Thomas, circa 1970s; 3 (Box 1559)
    - Eric Sloane, 1
    - Verso: Eric Sloane, 1-verso
  - Subject files: Frank Smith, undated; 4 (Box 1559)
    - Frank M. Smith, LT's wizard manager, 1
    - Note: Frank M. Smith, LT's wizard manager, 2
    - Photographed at the second Warner Academy broadcast, presented by the Gruen watch Company from Hollywood, are, left to right: _____ Sachs; Max Arnow, executive in charge of talent at Warner Brothers; Susan Hayward; Bruce Lester; Frank Smith, advertising manager of the Gruen Watch Company, and Owen Crump, producer of the program. The night's vehicle was "The King And The Chorus Girl," in which Miss Hayward and Mr. Lester were starred, 3
    - Verso: Photographed at the second Warner Academy broadcast, presented by the Gruen watch Company from Hollywood, are, left to right: _____ Sachs; Max Arnow, executive in charge of talent at Warner Brothers; Susan Hayward; Bruce Lester; Frank Smith, advertising manager of the Gruen Watch Company, and Owen Crump, producer of the program. The night's vehicle was "The King And The Chorus Girl," in which Miss Hayward and Mr. Lester were starred, 3-verso
    - [Three men standing behind a KFWB microphone], 4
    - [A group of men in suits], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas with a group at an event], 6
    - [Two men talking to a woman], 7
    - [Women talking], 8
  - Subject files: H. Allen Smith, circa 1968; 5 (Box 1559)
    - Caption: H. Allen Smith, author of BUSKIN' WITH H. ALLEN SMITH to be published 2 April 1968 ($4.95) Trident Press/630 Fifth Ave., N.Y.C/CI 5-6400, 1
  - Subject files: Janet Smith, circa 1935 - 1940; 6 (Box 1559)
    - [Janet Smith and Chimo], [note that states this is missing], 1
    - [Janet Smith and Chimo], [note that states this is missing], 2
    - [Janet Smith and Chimo], [note that states this is missing], 3
  - Subject files: Softball (barbecue), circa 1930s; 7 (Box 1559)
    - [Sir Hubert Wilkins, left, Lowell Thomas, right], 1
    - [Vilhjalmur Stefansson, left, Lowell Thomas, right], 2
    - Dr. Stefansson left, L.T. right, 3
    - Verso: Dr. Stefansson left, L.T. right, 3-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with a piece of paper], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas cooking], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas at a picnic table], 6
    - [Softball barbque], 7
    - [Making food for the softball barbeque], 8
    - [Entertainment at the softball barbque], 9
    - [People enjoying the softball barbque], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas making a speech at the softball barbeque], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas and others eating at the softball barbeque], 12
    - [Lowell Thomas and others at the softball barbeque], 13
    - [Lowell Thomas next to a man holding a dog], 14
  - Subject files: Softball (burros), undated; 8 (Box 1559)
    - Ed Reek, left, Lew Lehr, right, 1
    - Verso: Ed Reek, left, Lew Lehr, right, 1-verso
    - [Ed Reek, left, Lew Lehr, right], 2
    - Maj. James H. Doolittle, famous speed-flier, 3
    - Verso: Maj. James H. Doolittle, famous speed-flier, 3-verso
    - [Maj. James H. Doolittle, famous speed-flier], 4
    - Col. Lemuel Q. Stoopnagle [F. Chase Taylor] of radio fame, 5
    - Verso: Col. Lemuel Q. Stoopnagle [F. Chase Taylor] of radio fame, 5-verso
    - F. Chase Taylor, Col. Stoopnagle of radio fame, 6
    - Verso: F. Chase Taylor, Col. Stoopnagle of radio fame, 6-verso
    - [F. Chase Taylor, Col. Stoopnagle of radio fame], 7